export const quiz = {
  topic: 'Javascript',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 20,
  perQuestionScore: 5,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Number 1',
      choices: ['turkie', 'turky', 'turkey'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'turkey',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 2',
      choices: ['valley', 'valle', 'vally'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'valley',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 3',
      choices: ['dooty', 'duty', 'dudey'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'duty',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 4',
      choices: ['allie', 'ally', 'alley'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'alley',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 5',
      choices: ['lonely', 'loanly', 'lonly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'lonely',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 6',
      choices: ['haki', 'hockey', 'hocky'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'hockey',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 7',
      choices: ['drousy', 'drowzy', 'drowsy'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'drowsy',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 8',
      choices: ['fifty', 'fiftey', 'fivty'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'fifty',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 9',
      choices: ['coloni', 'colony', 'collony'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'colony',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 10',
      choices: ['stary', 'starey', 'starry'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'starry',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 11',
      choices: ['steddy', 'steady', 'stedde'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'steady',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 12',
      choices: ['melodie', 'melody', 'melady'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'melody',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 13',
      choices: ['hungery', 'hungary', 'hungry'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'hungry',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 14',
      choices: ['movie', 'moovey', 'moovi'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'movie',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 15',
      choices: ['chiminey', 'chimene', 'chimney'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'chimney',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 16',
      choices: ['plenti', 'plenty', 'plentey'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'plenty',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 17',
      choices: ['daily', 'daley', 'dayli'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'daily',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 18',
      choices: ['emptie', 'impty', 'empty'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'empty',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 19',
      choices: ['injury', 'injure', 'injurry'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'injury',
    },
    {
      question: 'Number 20',
      choices: ['prayrie', 'prairey', 'prairie'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'prairie',
    },
  ],
}